

# **MILAD EBRAHIMPOUR**

# **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Self-starting, enterprising digital marketer with 5+ years of experience.

I have strong technical skills as well as excellent interpersonal skills, enabling me to interact with a wide range of clients. I am eager to be challenged in order to grow and further improve my IT skills. My greatest passion in life is using my technical know-how to benefit other people and organisations.

#### **CORE COMPETENCIES**

- Strong networking and communication skills
- Managing offboarding employees
- · Proactive, initiative, creative and engaged

# **LICENSES & CERTIFICATIONS**

#### **General English**

The Manchester Metropolitan University ISSUED JUN 2022

# **CONTACT INFO**

epour.milad@gmail.com

07360567592

Palatine Rd, M20 2WG Manchester, United Kingdom

### **EDUCATION**

High School Diploma - Math

Iran - Tehran | 2009

CodeYourFuture - Softwere developer

Manchester Uk - 2022 - Presence

# LANGUAGES

100%

70%

70%

Persian-Farsi

English

Swedish

# **EXPERIENCE**

Funder - Desginer CYNOCO SWEDEN-STOCKHOLM SWEDEN Jan 2021 - Jan 2022 · 1 yr 1 mo

An application was designed to help Farsispeaking in Sweden to stay updated with the latest news and information about the market palace in Sweden.

#### **IT Support Specialist**

AMANDAS HEMTJÄNST- STOCKHOLM SWEDEN

Aug 2021 - Nov 2021 · 4 mos

Developing a website using WordPress, IT support, and coordinator.



# **MILAD EBRAHIMPOUR**

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Nursing Assistant**

ASSISTANS & HEMTJÄNST STOCKHOLM-STOCKHOLM SWEDEN Aug 2020 - Aug 2021 · 1 yr 1 mo

Served as a night shift nurse assistant.

#### **IT Manager**

SEPID HOLIDAY TRAVEL - STOCKHOLM SWEDEN Dec 2017 - Feb 2021 · 3 yrs 3 mos

Worked in IT department and customer service, developed website using WordPress.

# **PROJECTS**

#### **Beauty Florial Cosmetics & Perfumes**

UNITED ARAB EMIRATES Aug 2021 - Mar 2022

Developing an online-shop website using WordPress, managing social media, and online marketing strategy, and advertising.

www.beautyflorial.com

#### Body&i

UNITED KINGDOM Dec 2021 - Mar 2022

Managing social media, online marketing strategy, and growing up business through the online platforms.

www.bodyandi.uk

### **Caspian Deli and Grocery**

SWEDEN Feb 2022 - Feb 2022

Developing an online-shop website using WordPress

www.caspiandeli.se